Register of the Frederick L. Anderson papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Correspondence, 1938-1947
  - Alphabetical
    - Lieb, Helene, 1946 (Box-folder 8: 63)
    - Lindley, Ernest K., 1947 (Box-folder 8: 64)
    - Lindsay, Richard C., 1946 (Box-folder 8: 65)
    - Littel, Robert, 1946 (Box-folder 8: 66)
    - Lloyd, Hugh P., 1946 (Box-folder 8: 67)
    - Lodwick, Albert I., 1945-1947 (Box-folder 8: 68)
    - Longfellow, Newton, 1946 (Box-folder 8: 69)
    - Loud, Tremaine, 1946 (Box-folder 8: 70)
    - Love, Edgar P., 1946 (Box-folder 8: 71)
    - Lovett, Robert A., 1945-1946 (Box-folder 8: 72)
    - Lowe, Thomas M., 1946 (Box-folder 8: 73)
    - Luce, Henry R., 1947 (Box-folder 8: 74)
    - Ludlam, Douglas G., 1945 (Box-folder 8: 75)
    - Lumsden, Edith R., 1946 (Box-folder 8: 76)
    - Luper, James R., 1946 (Box-folder 8: 77)
    - Lyell, Van, 1946 (Box-folder 8: 78)
    - Lynch, Edmund C., 1946 (Box-folder 8: 79)
    - Lynch, John D., 1946 (Box-folder 8: 80)
    - Lynd, William E., 1942 (Box-folder 8: 81)
    - McAllister, Charles D., 1945 (Box-folder 9: 1)
    - McAndrews, Captain, 1946 (Box-folder 9: 2)
    - McCormick, John H., 1945-1946 (Box-folder 9: 3)
    - McCormick, Roger, 1945 (Box-folder 9: 4)
    - McDonald, George C., 1945-1946 (Box-folder 9: 5)
    - McElroy, James K., 1946 (Box-folder 9: 6)
    - McElroy, William, 1946 (Box-folder 9: 7)
    - McGreevy, Mrs. Milton, 1945 (Box-folder 9: 8)
    - McGuire, Jack, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 9: 9)
    - McKee, William, 1946 (Box-folder 9: 10)
    - McKenzie, Arthur, 1946 (Box-folder 9: 11)
    - McLaughry, James A., 1945-1946 (Box-folder 9: 12)
    - McLeod, J. C., 1946 (Box-folder 9: 13)
    - McNaughton, K. P., 1946 (Box-folder 9: 14)
    - McReynolds, W. R., 1945-1946 (Box-folder 9: 15)
    - Mahon, Pete, 1946 (Box-folder 9: 16)
    - Malone, P. W., 1946 (Box-folder 9: 17)
    - Manchester, MacArthur, 1947 (Box-folder 9: 18)
    - Mandel, Leon, 1947 (Box-folder 9: 19)
    - Mannheimer, M. J., 1947 (Box-folder 9: 20)
    - Martyn, John W., 1945 (Box-folder 9: 21)
    - Masefield, Peter, 1945 (Box-folder 9: 22)
    - Mason, G. L., 1946-1947 (Box-folder 9: 23)
    - Mason, William, 1947 (Box-folder 9: 24)
    - Mattison, Graham, 1946 (Box-folder 9: 25)
    - Mawefield, Peter, 1946 (Box-folder 9: 26)
    - Max, 1945 (Box-folder 9: 27)
    - Maxwell, Alfred R., 1945 (Box-folder 9: 28)
    - Maxwell, Howard H., 1947 (Box-folder 9: 29)
    - May, Andrew J., 1945 (Box-folder 9: 30)
    - Maylon, Charles, 1946 (Box-folder 9: 31)
    - Mercer, H. Glenn, 1946 (Box-folder 9: 32)
    - Mercer, Henry D., 1947 (Box-folder 9: 33)
    - Merriman, Hazel, 1947 (Box-folder 9: 34)
    - Messick, Allen G., 1947 (Box-folder 9: 35)
    - Michel, E. Jules, 1946 (Box-folder 9: 36)
    - Miller, Andrew, 1946 (Box-folder 9: 37)
    - Miller, Peter M., 1946 (Box-folder 9: 38)
    - Millett, Annie, 1945 (Box-folder 9: 39)
    - Milliken, Albert E., 1946-1947 (Box-folder 9: 40)
    - Milner, Edward, 1943 (Box-folder 9: 41)
    - Milner, Fred C., 1942 (Box-folder 9: 42)
    - Milstone, Maurice, 1945 (Box-folder 9: 43)
    - Mobley, Radford, 1947 (Box-folder 9: 44)
    - Moller, Joseph, 1945 (Box-folder 9: 45)
    - Montgomery, Henry G., 1945 (Box-folder 9: 46)
    - Montgomery, J. B., 1946-1947 (Box-folder 9: 47)
    - Moore, Aubry L., 1947 (Box-folder 9: 48)
    - Morgan, Herbert, 1946 (Box-folder 9: 49)
    - Morrison, H. Terry, 1945-1947 (Box-folder 9: 50)
    - Mow, Tsu Pang, 1945 (Box-folder 9: 51)
    - Mundy, George W., 1947 (Box-folder 9: 52)
    - Munson, Henry L., 1946 (Box-folder 9: 53)
    - Murphy, Charles, 1946 (Box-folder 9: 54)
    - Murphy, James F., 1946 (Box-folder 9: 55)
    - Murphy, Robert, 1945 (Box-folder 9: 56)
    - Myers, Charles T., 1945-1946 (Box-folder 9: 57)
    - Nacy, Richard R., 1946 (Box-folder 9: 58)
    - National Broadcasting Company, 1946 (Box-folder 9: 59)
    - Nazzaro, Joseph, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 9: 60)
    - Neblett, William H., 1946 (Box-folder 9: 61)
    - Nelson, M. R., 1947 (Box-folder 9: 62)
    - Neumann, Ruby A., 1946 (Box-folder 9: 63)
    - Neville, Michael J., 1946 (Box-folder 9: 64)
    - Newell, H. W., 1946-1947 (Box-folder 9: 65)
    - Nolan, F. J. Patrick, 1945-1947 (Box-folder 9: 66)
    - Nolan, Patrick, 1942 (Box-folder 9: 67)
    - Norcross, Carl, 1946 (Box-folder 9: 68)
    - Nordenskiold, Bengt, 1945 (Box-folder 9: 69)
    - Norstad, Lauris, 1943-1945 (Box-folder 9: 70)
    - Northrop, John K., 1942-1946 (Box-folder 9: 71)
    - Northwest Airlines, Inc., 1946 (Box-folder 9: 72)
    - Noyes, Edgar T., 1942 (Box-folder 9: 73)
    - Nugent, Richard E., 1946 (Box-folder 9: 74)
    - O'Connor, Frederick, 1946 (Box-folder 10: 1)
    - O'Daniel, W. Lee, 1946 (Box-folder 10: 2)
    - Odell, Herman, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 10: 3)
    - Odom, T. C., 1945 (Box-folder 10: 4)
    - Old, Archie J., 1945-1946 (Box-folder 10: 5)
    - Ordway, Lucius, 1945 (Box-folder 10: 6)
    - Ott, William, 1945 (Box-folder 10: 7)
    - Owen, Allison, 1946 (Box-folder 10: 8)
    - Paley, William S., 1945-1946 (Box-folder 10: 9)
    - Palm, John D., 1945 (Box-folder 10: 10)
    - Palmer, Perrine, 1947 (Box-folder 10: 11)
    - Palmer House, 1946 (Box-folder 10: 12)
    - Pardridge, William D., 1947 (Box-folder 10: 13)
    - Parham, Alfred H., 1946 (Box-folder 10: 14)
    - Parker, Brooks, 1946 (Box-folder 10: 15)
    - Parker, Lou, 1942 (Box-folder 10: 16)
    - Parks, Frederick L., 1946-1947 (Box-folder 10: 17)
    - Partridge, General, 1946 (Box-folder 10: 18)
    - Patterson, Paul, 1947 (Box-folder 10: 19)
    - Paul, W. J., 1947 (Box-folder 10: 20)
    - Peabody, Hume, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 10: 21)
    - Pearcy, Charles G., 1945-1946 (Box-folder 10: 22)
    - Pearson, Frederick S., 1945 (Box-folder 10: 23)
    - Perkinson, Allen C., 1946 (Box-folder 10: 24)
    - Perry, Farwell W., 1945-1947 (Box-folder 10: 25)
    - Perry, John, 1947 (Box-folder 10: 26)
    - Peters, John, 1945-1947 (Box-folder 10: 27)
    - Peterson, Val, 1947 (Box-folder 10: 28)
    - Pew, Joseph N., 1947 (Box-folder 10: 29)
    - Picher, Oliver S., 1947 (Box-folder 10: 30)
    - Pierson, H. L., 1945 (Box-folder 10: 31)
    - Pincus, I. N., 1946 (Box-folder 10: 32)
    - Pinkley, Virgil, 1945 (Box-folder 10: 33)
    - Pittenger, James S., 1945-1947 (Box-folder 10: 34)
    - Pitts, Younger A., 1946 (Box-folder 10: 35)
    - Pizzuto, Joseph R., 1945-1947 (Box-folder 10: 36)
    - Plummer, Everett C., 1942 (Box-folder 10: 37)
    - Plummer, William L., 1946 (Box-folder 10: 38)
    - Pond, Everett L., 1945 (Box-folder 10: 39)
    - Pool, J. Henry, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 10: 40)
    - Portal, Charles, 1945 (Box-folder 10: 41)
    - Potter, Thomas K., 1946 (Box-folder 10: 42)
    - Powell, Lewis F., 1945-1947 (Box-folder 10: 43)
    - Pratt and Whitney Aircraft, 1946 (Box-folder 10: 44)
    - Preston, Maurice A., 1946 (Box-folder 10: 45)
    - Proctor, Robert, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 10: 46)
    - Pryor, Robert N., 1947 (Box-folder 10: 47)
    - Pulk, Eugene L., 1945 (Box-folder 10: 48)
    - Quesada, Elwood R., 1946 (Box-folder 10: 49)
    - Quinn, John T., 1946 (Box-folder 10: 50)
    - Ramey, Roger M., 1946 (Box-folder 10: 51)
    - Randall, Russell E., 1946 (Box-folder 10: 52)
    - Randolph, Jennings, 1946 (Box-folder 10: 53)
    - Rankin, Fred, 1946 (Box-folder 10: 54)
    - Razey, Scott, 1947 (Box-folder 10: 55)
    - Read, Ingraham, 1946 (Box-folder 10: 56)
    - Reed, Daniel, 1946 (Box-folder 10: 57)
    - Reed, Walter J., 1945 (Box-folder 10: 58)
    - Rees, Clifford, 1946 (Box-folder 10: 59)
    - Resce, Walter, 1946 (Box-folder 10: 60)
    - Reynolds, E. D., 1942 (Box-folder 10: 61)
    - Reynolds, Harrison G., 1945-1946 (Box-folder 10: 62)
    - Rhine, Bertrand, 1947 (Box-folder 10: 63)
    - Richards, J. S., 1942 (Box-folder 10: 64)
    - Richards, Walter E., 1945-1947 (Box-folder 10: 65)
    - Richardson, John W., 1946 (Box-folder 10: 66)
    - Ricks, Earl T., 1946-1947 (Box-folder 10: 67)
    - Riddle Company, 1947 (Box-folder 10: 68)
    - Riedel, Bertha, 1946 (Box-folder 10: 69)
    - Riley, Mrs. Catherine, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 10: 70)
    - Ritchie, William, 1946 (Box-folder 10: 71)
    - Rivero, James, 1945 (Box-folder 10: 72)
    - Robart, Ralph W., 1946 (Box-folder 10: 73)
    - Robb, James, 1945 (Box-folder 10: 74)
    - Robbins, A. S., 1946 (Box-folder 10: 75)
    - Roberts, Godfrey, 1946 (Box-folder 10: 76)
    - Roberts, Jack, 1947 (Box-folder 10: 77)
    - Roberts, James E., 1946-1947 (Box-folder 10: 78)
    - Roberts, Thomas B., 1946-1947 (Box-folder 10: 79)
    - Robertson, Claude W., 1946 (Box-folder 10: 80)
    - Robinson, Alan, 1942 (Box-folder 10: 81)
    - Rochester, Charles E., 1945 (Box-folder 10: 82)
    - Rochford, E. P., 1945 (Box-folder 10: 83)
    - Rogers, Pat, 1946 (Box-folder 10: 84)
    - Roosevelt, Elliott, 1945 (Box-folder 10: 85)
    - Rose, Bernard C., 1946 (Box-folder 10: 86)
    - Rosenblatt, Sol A., 1945-1947 (Box-folder 10: 87)
    - Rosser, William, 1946 (Box-folder 10: 88)
    - Rostow, Walter, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 10: 89)
    - Rouch, A. J., 1947 (Box-folder 10: 90)
    - Royall, Kenneth C., 1945 (Box-folder 10: 91)
    - Royce, Ralph, 1945 (Box-folder 10: 92)
    - Sagendorph, Kent, 1946 (Box-folder 11: 1)
    - Salinas, Gustavo, 1946 (Box-folder 11: 2)
    - Samarin, Timofei, 1946 (Box-folder 11: 3)
    - Samford, John A., 1947 (Box-folder 11: 4)
    - Sams, William C., 1945 (Box-folder 11: 5)
    - Santora, William, 1947 (Box-folder 11: 6)
    - Sarnoff, David, 1946 (Box-folder 11: 7)
    - Saturday Evening Post, 1946 (Box-folder 11: 8)
    - Saunders, Homer L., 1946 (Box-folder 11: 9)
    - Saunders, La Verne, 1947 (Box-folder 11: 10)
    - Saundling, Air Marshal, 1946 (Box-folder 11: 11)
    - Schatz, Jay, 1946 (Box-folder 11: 12)
    - Scherbak, H., 1946 (Box-folder 11: 13)
    - Scherer, Harris F., 1945 (Box-folder 11: 14)
    - Schlatter, David M., 1945-1947 (Box-folder 11: 15)
    - Schmick, W. F., 1947 (Box-folder 11: 16)
    - Schroeder, Hugo, 1942 (Box-folder 11: 17)
    - Schurter, Orie O., 1946 (Box-folder 11: 18)
    - Scott, J. Y., 1946 (Box-folder 11: 19)
    - Seligson, William, 1946 (Box-folder 11: 20)
    - Selway, Robert R., 1946-1947 (Box-folder 11: 21)
    - Seversky, Alexander de, 1943-1946 (Box-folder 11: 22)
    - Shapiro, Louis, 1942 (Box-folder 11: 23)
    - Shattuck School, 1946 (Box-folder 11: 24)
    - Shea, A. F., 1945-1946 (Box-folder 11: 25)
    - Sheffield, T. C., 1947 (Box-folder 11: 26)
    - Sheldon, Huntington D., 1947 (Box-folder 11: 27)
    - Shepard, Gracie L., 1945 (Box-folder 11: 28)
    - Sherburne, T. L., 1947 (Box-folder 11: 29)
    - Sheridan, John E., 1946 (Box-folder 11: 30)
    - Sherry, Alden, 1945-1947 (Box-folder 11: 31)
    - Shields, W. A., 1946 (Box-folder 11: 32)
    - Shupack, Ben, 1946 (Box-folder 11: 33)
    - Silcox, C. N., 1947 (Box-folder 11: 34)
    - Simms, John F., 1947 (Box-folder 11: 35)
    - Simons, John H., 1947 (Box-folder 11: 36)
    - Sims, T. A., 1946-1947 (Box-folder 11: 37)
    - Simpson, Roy, 1946 (Box-folder 11: 38)
    - Sleeper, Raymond S., 1946 (Box-folder 11: 39)
    - Slessor, John C., 1945-1947 (Box-folder 11: 40)
    - Smart, Jacob E., 1945-1947 (Box-folder 11: 41)
    - Smethills, John A., 1947 (Box-folder 11: 42)
    - Smith, Bettie, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 11: 43)
    - Smith, C. R., 1945-1947 (Box-folder 11: 44)
    - Smith, Constance, 1946 (Box-folder 11: 45)
    - Smith, Dan T., 1946 (Box-folder 11: 46)
    - Smith, F. H., 1946-1947 (Box-folder 11: 47)
    - Smith, Fred, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 11: 48)
    - Smith, Joseph, 1946 (Box-folder 11: 49)
    - Smith, Leonard F., 1945 (Box-folder 11: 50)
    - Smith, Luther S., 1945 (Box-folder 11: 51)
    - Smith, M. L., 1946 (Box-folder 11: 52)
    - Smith, Marie, 1946 (Box-folder 11: 53)
    - Smith, Rex, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 11: 54)
    - Smith, Robert J., 1946-1947 (Box-folder 11: 55)
    - Smith, Vernon L., 1946 (Box-folder 11: 56)
    - Smith, Waddell, 1946 (Box-folder 11: 57)
    - Smith, W. J., 1946 (Box-folder 11: 58)
    - Snavely, Ralph A., 1940-1946 (Box-folder 11: 59)
    - Snyder, Fred, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 11: 60)
    - Snyder, Walter D., 1947 (Box-folder 11: 61)
    - Solheim, Henry, 1946 (Box-folder 11: 62)
    - Sorensen, Colonel, 1942 (Box-folder 11: 63)
    - Sorensen, E. P., 1943 (Box-folder 11: 64)
    - Spaatz, Carl, 1944-1946 (Box-folder 11: 65)
    - Spaatz, Mrs. Carl, 1947 (Box-folder 11: 66)
    - Spaight, R. H. S., 1942 (Box-folder 11: 67)
    - Spencer, H. B., 1945 (Box-folder 11: 68)
    - Spivey, Delmar T., 1946-1947 (Box-folder 11: 69)
    - Sproull, Merle, 1946 (Box-folder 11: 70)
    - Spry, James W., 1945 (Box-folder 11: 71)
    - Stalder, Marvin F., 1947 (Box-folder 12: 1)
    - Stalnaker, George W., 1945 (Box-folder 12: 2)
    - Stark, John, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 12: 3)
    - Stark, Louis B., 1942 (Box-folder 12: 4)
    - Stearley, Ralph, 1946 (Box-folder 12: 5)
    - Stella, Able, 1946 (Box-folder 12: 6)
    - Stern, Ed, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 12: 7)
    - Stevenson, John D., 1946 (Box-folder 12: 8)
    - Stewart, Senator, 1946 (Box-folder 12: 9)
    - Stone, Charles B., 1947 (Box-folder 12: 10)
    - Stone, George, 1947 (Box-folder 12: 11)
    - Stovall, Howard, 1945 (Box-folder 12: 12)
    - Stovall, Willaim H., 1945-1947 (Box-folder 12: 13)
    - Stratemeyer, George E., 1937-1947 (Box-folder 12: 14)
    - Street, Bill, 1947 (Box-folder 12: 15)
    - Sullivan, Gael, 1947 (Box-folder 12: 16)
    - Sullivan, John Dwight, 1945-1947 (Box-folder 12: 17)
    - Summersby, Kathleen, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 12: 18)
    - Swanson, Gilbert C., 1946-1947 (Box-folder 12: 19)
    - Sweeney, Bo (Cox and Stevens Aircraft Corporation), 1942 (Box-folder 12: 20)
    - Symington, W. Stuart, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 12: 21)
    - Tangye, Nigel, 1946 (Box-folder 12: 22)
    - Tappan, Alan P., 1946 (Box-folder 12: 23)
    - Taylor, Charles M., 1946 (Box-folder 12: 24)
    - Taylor, Elizabeth, 1947 (Box-folder 12: 25)
    - Taylor, H. C., 1947 (Box-folder 12: 26)
    - Taylor, Henry J., 1947 (Box-folder 12: 27)
    - Taylor, Maxwell D., 1946-1947 (Box-folder 12: 28)
    - Taylor, Yantis, 1946 (Box-folder 12: 29)
    - Tedder, Lord, 1946 (Box-folder 12: 30)
    - Thomas, Arthur, 1945 (Box-folder 12: 31)
    - Thomas, Fay M., 1946-1947 (Box-folder 12: 32)
    - Thomas, Jay P., 1946 (Box-folder 12: 33)
    - Thomas, Lowell, 1946 (Box-folder 12: 34)
    - Thompson, Charles, 1945 (Box-folder 12: 35)
    - Thornton, Charles B., 1946 (Box-folder 12: 36)
    - Thruelsen, Richard, 1945 (Box-folder 12: 37)
    - Tibier, Luciens, 1947 (Box-folder 12: 38)
    - Tilley, Barbara, 1946 (Box-folder 12: 39)
    - Tillinghast, T. E., 1946 (Box-folder 12: 40)
    - Timberlake, Patrick W., 1946 (Box-folder 12: 41)
    - Tindall, Lorry, 1947 (Box-folder 12: 42)
    - Tipton, S. G., 1945 (Box-folder 12: 43)
    - Todd, Raymond P., 1945 (Box-folder 12: 44)
    - Todd, Walter E., 1946 (Box-folder 12: 45)
    - Towle, Steward W., 1946 (Box-folder 12: 46)
    - Travis, Robert, 1946 (Box-folder 12: 47)
    - Trenchard, Lord, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 12: 48)
    - Truesdell, Karl, 1945 (Box-folder 12: 49)
    - Tubbs, W. L., 1946 (Box-folder 12: 50)
    - Tulloch, A. R., 1946 (Box-folder 12: 51)
    - Tunner, William H., 1947 (Box-folder 12: 52)
    - Turner, Howard M., 1945 (Box-folder 12: 53)
    - Turner, Roscoe, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 12: 54)
    - Tuttle, Louisa, 1945 (Box-folder 12: 55)
    - Twining, N. F., 1946-1947 (Box-folder 12: 56)
    - Umla, Charles, 1947 (Box-folder 13: 1)
    - Usher, G. L., 1938 (Box-folder 13: 2)
    - Vanaman, A. W., 1945-1946 (Box-folder 13: 3)
    - VanCronkhite, John, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 13: 4)
    - Vandenberg, Hoyt, 1946 (Box-folder 13: 5)
    - Van der Weil, J., 1946 (Box-folder 13: 6)
    - Vetlesen, 1946 (Box-folder 13: 7)
    - Vidal, F. L., 1946 (Box-folder 13: 8)
    - Vincent, Clinton D., 1946 (Box-folder 13: 9)
    - Vining, Robert E., 1945 (Box-folder 13: 10)
    - Voss, T. S., 1946 (Box-folder 13: 11)
    - Wainright, Jonathan, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 13: 12)
    - Waldrop, Frank, 1947 (Box-folder 13: 13)
    - Walker, A. L., 1945 (Box-folder 13: 14)
    - Walker, Kenneth M., 1939-1942 (Box-folder 13: 15)
    - Walker, Mrs. R. R., 1942 (Box-folder 13: 16)
    - Walsh, Robert, 1945-1947 (Box-folder 13: 17)
    - War Bond Committee of Kingston, New York, 1945 (Box-folder 13: 18)
    - Warner, Milo, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 13: 19)
    - Watt, R. J., 1946 (Box-folder 13: 20)
    - Watt, Mrs. R. J., 1946 (Box-folder 13: 21)
    - Weatherhead, Albert J., 1946 (Box-folder 13: 22)
    - Webb, A. N., 1946 (Box-folder 13: 23)
    - Wehle, Ruth, 1946 (Box-folder 13: 24)
    - Weicker, Lowell, 1945-1947 (Box-folder 13: 25)
    - Weldon, Sam V., 1946 (Box-folder 13: 26)
    - Welsh, William W., 1946-1947 (Box-folder 13: 27)
    - West, C. C., 1947 (Box-folder 13: 28)
    - Wherry, Kenneth S., 1947 (Box-folder 13: 29)
    - White, J. W., 1945 (Box-folder 13: 30)
    - White, Thomas D., 1947 (Box-folder 13: 31)
    - Whitehead, Mrs. Charles, 1946 (Box-folder 13: 32)
    - Whitehead, Ennis, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 13: 33)
    - Whiting, Lawrence H., 1946 (Box-folder 13: 34)
    - Whitman, LeRoy, 1947 (Box-folder 13: 35)
    - Whitney, John H., 1946-1947 (Box-folder 13: 36)
    - Whitten, L. P., 1946 (Box-folder 13: 37)
    - Wickersham, Cornelius, 1945 (Box-folder 13: 38)
    - Wilkins, Colonel, 1946 (Box-folder 13: 39)
    - Williams, L. Kemper, 1946 (Box-folder 13: 40)
    - Williams, Paul L., 1945 (Box-folder 13: 41)
    - Williams, Robert B., 1945 (Box-folder 13: 42)
    - Williamson, Charles G., 1945-1947 (Box-folder 13: 43)
    - Williamson, Glen, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 13: 44)
    - Williamson, R. E. S., 1946 (Box-folder 13: 45)
    - Wilson, Delmar E., 1946 (Box-folder 13: 46)
    - Wilson, Donald, 1946 (Box-folder 13: 47)
    - Wilson, James W., 1945-1946 (Box-folder 13: 48)
    - Winant, John G., 1945-1946 (Box-folder 13: 49)
    - Wings Club, 1945 (Box-folder 13: 50)
    - Wolf, Paul W., 1945 (Box-folder 13: 51)
    - Wood, James I., 1945 (Box-folder 13: 52)
    - Woodward, Helen, 1945 (Box-folder 13: 53)
    - Wrigglesworth, William J., 1945-1947 (Box-folder 13: 54)
    - Wright, W. H., 1946 (Box-folder 13: 55)
    - Wriston, Roscoe C., 1946 (Box-folder 13: 56)
    - Wurtsmith, 1945 (Box-folder 13: 57)
    - Wyler, William, 1946 (Box-folder 13: 58)
    - Yost, Emmett F., 1945 (Box-folder 13: 59)
    - Yount, Barton K., 1945 (Box-folder 13: 60)
    - Zagelow, George E., 1946 (Box-folder 13: 61)
    - Zetzmann, William G., 1945-1946 (Box-folder 13: 62)
    - Zielinski, Constantine E., 1946 (Box-folder 13: 63)
    - Zimmerman, Don, 1946 (Box-folder 13: 64)
    - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 13: 65-66)
- Chronological File, 1942-1945
  Correspondence, memoranda, reports, charts, studies, printed matter and clippings, arranged chronologically. Included is an index to the file covering the time period June 1943 through December 1944.
  - Index, 1943 June - 1944 December (Box-folder 14: 1-6)
  - 1942 (Box-folder 15: 1)
  - 1943
    - January (Box-folder 15: 2-3)
    - February (Box-folder 15: 4)
    - March (Box-folder 15: 5)
    - April (Box-folder 15: 6)
    - May (Box-folder 15: 7)
    - June (Box-folder 15: 8)
    - July (Box-folder 15: 9)
    - August (Box-folder 15: 10)
    - September (Box-folder 16: 1)
    - October (Box-folder 16: 2)
    - November (Box-folder 16: 3-4)
    - December (Box-folder 16: 5-6)
    - December (Box-folder 17: 1)
  - 1944
    - January 1 (Box-folder 17: 2)
    - January 2-7 (Box-folder 17: 3)
    - January 8-17 (Box-folder 17: 4)
    - January 18-26 (Box-folder 17: 5)
    - January 27 - February 2 (Box-folder 17: 6)
    - February 3-10 (Box-folder 18: 1)
    - February 10-19 (Box-folder 18: 2)
    - February 20-27 (Box-folder 18: 3)
    - February 28 - March 3 (Box-folder 18: 4)
    - March 4-9 (Box-folder 18: 5)
    - March 10-18 (Box-folder 19: 1)
    - March 19-26 (Box-folder 19: 2)
    - March 27-31 (Box-folder 19: 3)
    - April 1-6 (Box-folder 19: 4)
    - April 7-10 (Box-folder 19: 5)
    - April 11-16 (Box-folder 20: 1)
    - April 17-22 (Box-folder 20: 2)
    - April 23-29 (Box-folder 20: 3)
    - April 30 - May 2 (Box-folder 20: 4)
    - May 3-7 (Box-folder 20: 5)
    - May 8-13 (Box-folder 20: 6)
    - May 14-19 (Box-folder 20: 7)
    - May 20-23 (Box-folder 21: 1)
    - May 24-28 (Box-folder 21: 2)
    - May 29-31 (Box-folder 21: 3)
    - June 1-5 (Box-folder 21: 4)
    - June 6-7 (Box-folder 21: 5)
    - June 8-10 (Box-folder 21: 6)
    - June 11-13 (Box-folder 21: 7)
    - June 14-18 (Box-folder 22: 1)
    - June 19-22 (Box-folder 22: 2)
    - June 23-27 (Box-folder 22: 3)
    - June 28-30 (Box-folder 22: 4)
    - July 1-4 (Box-folder 22: 5)
    - July 5-7 (Box-folder 22: 6)
    - July 8-10 (Box-folder 22: 7)
    - July 11-13 (Box-folder 23: 1)
    - July 14-16 (Box-folder 23: 2)
    - July 17-18 (Box-folder 23: 3)
    - July 19-21 (Box-folder 23: 4)
    - July 22-23 (Box-folder 23: 5)
    - July 24-25 (Box-folder 23: 6)
    - July 25 (Box-folder 24: 1-2)
    - July 26-27 (Box-folder 24: 3)
    - July 28 (Box-folder 24: 4)
    - July 29-30 (Box-folder 24: 5)
    - July 30-31 (Box-folder 24: 6)
    - August 1-2 (Box-folder 25: 1)
    - August 3-4 (Box-folder 25: 2)
    - August 5 (Box-folder 25: 3)
    - August 6 (Box-folder 25: 4)
    - August 7 (Box-folder 25: 5)
    - August 8 (Box-folder 25: 6)
    - August 9 (Box-folder 26: 1)
    - August 10 (Box-folder 26: 2)
    - August 11-12 (Box-folder 26: 3)
    - August 13-14 (Box-folder 26: 4)
    - August 15-16 (Box-folder 26: 5)
    - August 17-18 (Box-folder 26: 6)
    - August 19-20 (Box-folder 27: 1)
    - August 21 (Box-folder 27: 2)
    - August 22-23 (Box-folder 27: 3)
    - August 24-25 (Box-folder 27: 4)
    - August 26-28 (Box-folder 27: 5)
    - August 29-30 (Box-folder 28: 1)
    - August 31 (Box-folder 28: 2)
    - September 1 (Box-folder 28: 3)
    - September 2 (Box-folder 28: 4)
    - September 3 (Box-folder 28: 5)
    - September 4 (Box-folder 28: 6)
    - September 5 (Box-folder 28: 7)
    - September 6 (Box-folder 28: 8-9)
    - September 7-8 (Box-folder 29: 1)
    - September 9-10 (Box-folder 29: 2)
    - September 11 (Box-folder 29: 3)
    - September 12 (Box-folder 29: 4)
    - September 13-14 (Box-folder 29: 5)
    - September 15 (Box-folder 29: 6)
    - September 16-17 (Box-folder 29: 7)
    - September 18 (Box-folder 30: 1)
    - September 19 (Box-folder 30: 2)
    - September 20-21 (Box-folder 30: 3)
    - September 22-23 (Box-folder 30: 4)
    - September 24-25 (Box-folder 30: 5)
    - September 26 (Box-folder 30: 6)
    - September 27 (Box-folder 30: 7)
    - September 28 (Box-folder 30: 8)
    - September 29 (Box-folder 31: 1)
    - September 30 (Box-folder 31: 2)
    - October 1 (Box-folder 31: 3)
    - October 2 (Box-folder 31: 4)
    - October 3 (Box-folder 31: 5)
    - October 4-5 (Box-folder 31: 6)
    - October 6 (Box-folder 31: 7)
    - October 7-8 (Box-folder 31: 8)
    - October 9 (Box-folder 32: 1)
    - October 10 (Box-folder 32: 2)
    - October 11 (Box-folder 32: 3)
    - October 12 (Box-folder 32: 4)
    - October 13 (Box-folder 32: 5)
    - October 14 (Box-folder 32: 6)
    - October 15 (Box-folder 32: 7-8)
    - October 16-17 (Box-folder 32: 9)
    - October 18-19 (Box-folder 33: 1)
    - October 20 (Box-folder 33: 2)
    - October 21-22 (Box-folder 33: 3)
    - October 23 (Box-folder 33: 4)
    - October 24 (Box-folder 33: 5)
    - October 25 (Box-folder 33: 6)
    - October 26 (Box-folder 33: 7)
    - October 27 (Box-folder 34: 1)
    - October 28 (Box-folder 34: 2)
    - October 29 (Box-folder 34: 3)
    - October 30 (Box-folder 34: 4)
    - October 31 (Box-folder 34: 5-6)
    - November 1 (Box-folder 34: 7-8)
    - November 2 (Box-folder 35: 1)
    - November 3 (Box-folder 35: 2)
    - November 4 (Box-folder 35: 3)
    - November 5 (Box-folder 35: 4-5)